<view autoCancelInterval="90" isVisible="true" onunloadCancelJobs="true" template="dashboard.html" isSticky="False">

    <label>Introduction</label>
    <module name="AccountBar" layoutPanel="appHeader" />
   <module name="SideviewUtils" layoutPanel="appHeader" />
  <module name="AppBar" layoutPanel="appHeader" />
 
<module name="URLLoader" layoutPanel="viewHeader" autoRun="True">
    
  <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="panel_row1_col1">
    <param name="html"><![CDATA[

<div class="home">

      <H2> What does this part of the App do?</h2>
<center>   <img src="/static/app/mysginfo/banner.jpg"> </a> </center>
<p>Road users are usually updated by the traffic status through technology means such as radio, internet etc. But, do they know what’s causing these congestions? In addition, would you like to know what’s the current car park lots availability figure for each commercial building in the city area? 
</p>
<p>Our application does just that. </p>
<p>One of T&C app’s capabilities is that it lets you get updated on the car park lots figures on a 5 minute real time update. This means that you are able to view the current number of parking lots that’s available. These data are updated every five minutes, so you won’t be viewing the same data every time you run our application. The figures that we are able to provide are mostly from the city area, such as Marina, Harbour front and Orchard Road. Hence, if you are heading to Hotels, Shopping Centres or other commercial buildings, do visit our application beforehand!
</p>
<p>Our application’s capability does not stop there. It also provides a platform for you to know what causes the current congestions occurring on the roads of our island. For example, there was a slow moving traffic jam happening on the Paya Lebar flyover and, you are interested to know what happened. Our application is able to display out the cause, such as road works or an accident so that it can help you decide if you need a detour to your destination.
</p>
<p>
For the maps visualisation, you might not be able to view it if you have not downloaded the Google Maps for Splunk app. You can download the app <a href="http://splunk-base.splunk.com/apps/22365/google-maps">HERE</a>.
      

  </div>
    ]]></param>
  </module>

    <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="panel_row1_col2">
      <param name="html"><![CDATA[
  <div class="home">
   
 <h2> Application Requirements: </h2>


<p> Before you could benefit from our application's capabilities, there are few configurations that needs to be done beforehand. These configurations only requires you to key in the necessary credentials and information about yourself. Since our application pulls real life data from Singapore’s Land Transport Authorities, hence you need to provide us with three main inputs before our app can function the way it should. <br/> </p>
The three inputs are –  <br/><br/>
<ul>
<li> Name </li><br/>

<li> Account Key </li><br/>

<li> Unique User ID </li><br/></ul>

<p> These credential inputs will allow the application to run smoothly. The first input is your Name. You can choose any name that you prefer to be recognize as. The second input is the Account Key. This key is the set of characters that you have been provided by LTA upon your request. With the Account key, you can now generate the Unique User ID that will be needed during the configurations later. If you have not requested for the Account Key, you may follow this guide to do so:</p>
<a href=” http://www.mytransport.sg/content/mytransport/home/dataMall.html”> <u>Guide to request for Account Key</u> </a><br/> 

<p> Once you have gotten a hold of these required fields, you can now begin the configurations. <br/>(Menu Nav > Carpark Lots Availability/Traffic Informations > Carpark/Traffic Credential Inputs)  </p>
<br>
<b> Good Luck! </b> <br/>


  </div>
   ]]></param>   
  </module>

  <module name="Search" layoutPanel="panel_row1_col1">
  
      <module name="Search">
        <param name="search">
        | inputlookup splunk_instances_info | search $sos_server$
        </param>
        <module name="ResultsValueSetter">
          <param name="fields">host_fqdn, total_phys_mem_gb, cpu_count, version, build, os_name, cpu_arch, SPLUNK_HOME, SPLUNK_DB, license_role, auth_method</param>

          
        </module>
      </module>
    </module>
 <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="panel_row2_col1">
   <param name="html"><![CDATA[

    <div>
        <div class="home" style="float:left">
        <h2>my<u><b>SG</b></u>info is your app!</h2>
	<p>Is there anything that you find annoying about our app? We'd love to know!</p>
        <p>To request features, provide feedback, or report issues, send email to <b><a href="mailto:mySGinfo@splunk.com">mySGinfo@splunk.com</a></b>.</p>

	<p>TnC has been developed primarily by the Splunk Support team, with the help of Splunk Dev, Splunk Docs, and <b><a href="http://sideviewapps.com" class="spl-icon-external-link-xsm" target="_blank">Sideview LLC</a></b>.</p>
        </div>
        <div style="float:right">
        <a href="http://www.lta.gov.sg"><img src="/static/app/mysginfo/people.png" alt="mySGinfo"/></a>
        </div>
    </div>
   ]]></param>   
  </module>
    </module>

 
  
   
 
  


</view>